Comparando archivos TEST\singleone.txt y TEST2\SINGLEONE.TXT
***** TEST\singleone.txt
If you pass everything as a string, then your command is passed to the shell; 
las chicas no tienen pilila
if you pass them as a list then you don't need to worry about escaping anything. See
***** TEST2\SINGLEONE.TXT
If you pass everything as a string, then your command is passed to the shell; 
if you pass them as a list then you don't need to worry about escaping anything. See
*****

Comparando archivos TEST\PELILA\jajasik.txt y TEST2\PELILA\JAJASIK.TXT
FC: no se han encontrado diferencias

Comparando archivos TEST\PELILA\notepad++.exe y TEST2\PELILA\NOTEPAD++.EXE
FC: no se han encontrado diferencias

Comparando archivos TEST\PELILA\THIRDLEVEL\gunsout.txt y TEST2\PELILA\THIRDLEVEL\GUNSOUT.TXT
FC: no se han encontrado diferencias

The file pelila\elchocu.txt does not exist on test2 

